All right, let's welcome in LT Overton,
your newest Dallas Cowboy out of
Alabama. LT, how are you?
Congratulations. Welcome to the Dallas
Cowboys, my man.
>> I appreciate it. I'm good. I feel more
than blessed getting to go back home.
>> Yeah, this is this is awesome. It's
really exciting. We've been breaking you
down. We got to have one of the Cowboy
scouts, Eric Ellingsworth, come in here.
He was super excited to get you. H how
has this process been for you? How much
contact did you have with Dallas? Was
this a team that you were really hoping
to be drafted by?
>> Oh yeah, most definitely. Um the process
was definitely a long process, but a
process that I definitely needed to go
through. Um me and anybody going to win
this 2026 draft. um from the from the
combine to you know pro day and the
senior bowl like I I've always had a
feeling that the Cowboys had an eye on
me and they've always they they they
have been keeping in contact since the
Senior Bowl after our play after our
little playoff run and since then like
it's it's just been constant
communication.
>> Alt congratulations and welcome to
Dallas. in those conversations or any
meetings that you've had with Dallas and
their staff up to this point, what has
their communication with you been as to
where they see you fitting into
Christian Parker's defense?
>> Um, they love me, they love how
versatile I am um as a as a deferment.
You know, being able to not just play
the edge and dropping coverage, but also
being able to move into that 32 uh and
play that four on the inside. They like
they like me. I've been hearing a lot
about the big end. Um been hearing big
fit, but yeah.
>> LT, you play with it looks like a lot of
power. Um and that just really seems to
stand out the way that you know you you
play against the run. Do you take pride
in just, you know, doing those little
things and and playing in in those
spaces that are or maybe not the
flashes, but you just come in there with
relentless effort, lot of power, and and
looking to stop the run.
without a doubt. Ever since I ever since
I stepped on to campus in Alabama, you
know, that power that power aspect of
the game and not just that, but that run
stop is has really been my bread and
butter. Um, something I really take
pride in is being able to, you know, you
got to stop the run before they start
throwing passes, especially how the SEC,
but, you know, just being able to open
up, you know, open up the opportunity
for it to be more pass play. That's
That's why I love him.
>> Hey, LT, congrats. Uh, you're reuniting
with Tyler Booker. How cool is that
going to be for you,
>> man? That's going to be amazing. I I
missed him. So, I missed him so much.
Like, I know how great great of a leader
he is. And just being being able to be
under his wing, knowing how how he is,
and he already got a little bit of a
feel in the NFL, I thought it would be
good, dude. Just two. How great is it
just for you LT the opportunity to come
in here play along a defensive line that
already has such like really established
big- time, you know, players like uh
Quinnon Williams, former Alabama guy.
Um, you know, Kenny Clark. How
significant is that for you just to be
able to play alongside them and learn
from them?
>> I mean, it means a lot to me. Like the
these NFL, these guys been these guys
been in the league really probably as
long as I've been playing football. Um,
and just that information that just that
knowledge alone can tell you how much
how much knowledge and you know skill
they could they could pour into me since
I step on you know step into the
facility. Like guys like that I've
always I've always poured into
especially um transman had guys like DVR
2K they they helped me through the they
help me through the way show me the
ropes. You know, you got guys like like
you were sending Dex to Mars. I know
he's been showing me the ropes while I
get there, too. So, all props to them.
>> We're talking with newest Cowboy
defensive lineman LT Overton here on
1053 the fan in Dallascowboys.com. So,
LT, outside of football,
what what's something about you? What
what do you like to do to unwind?
>> Man, I love going bowling. Um, I
actually want do want to end up joining
a bowling league when I'm done with it.
>> There we go. Cool. I I picked up I
picked up you know saying Alabama you
know I started hunting fishing too.
>> Here we go
ATV ride you know being out in the
countryside.
>> Now are you more of like you want to
find a bowling alley that's like new up
and done or you want to f find like the
old like rundown smells like cigarette
smoke. I just want to find my bowl and
roll that thing.
>> I I like it original.
>> Okay. All right.
them old school. Yeah. You know, the
slick, you know, the slick on the on the
lane is gonna be gonna be right at the
old school.
>> Might slip on a Marlboro Red or
something.
Yeah.
>> Well, LT, thank you so much, man.
Congratulations. We're so happy to have
you here in Dallas. Have a great rest of
the day and we'll see you here soon.